https://expertmc.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyAchieving the Impossible – ExpertMC.com  is committed to providing quality services to you and this policy outlines our ongoing obligations to you in respect of how we manage your Personal Information.We have adopted the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the Privacy Act). The NPPs govern the way in which we collect, use, disclose, store, secure and dispose of your Personal Information.A copy of the Australian Privacy Principles may be obtained from the website of The Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at www.aoic.gov.auWhat is Personal Information and why do we collect it?Personal Information is information or an opinion that identifies an individual. Examples of Personal Information we collect include: names, addresses, email addresses, phone and facsimile numbers.This Personal Information is obtained in many ways including interviews, correspondence, by telephone and facsimile, by email, via our website www.expertMC.com, from your website, from media and publications, from other publicly available sources, from cookies and from third parties. We don’t guarantee website links or policy of authorised third parties.We collect your Personal Information for the primary purpose of providing our services to you and marketing. We may also use your Personal Information for secondary purposes closely related to the primary purpose, in circumstances where you would reasonably expect such use or disclosure. You may unsubscribe from our mailing/marketing lists at any time by using the Unsubscribe Button provided on every mailing we send out.When we collect Personal Information we will, where appropriate and where possible, explain to you why we are collecting the information and how we plan to use it.Sensitive InformationSensitive information is defined in the Privacy Act to include information or opinion about such things as an individual’s racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership of a trade union or other professional body, criminal record or health information.Sensitive information will be used by us only:For the primary purpose for which it was obtainedFor a secondary purpose that is directly related to the primary purposeWith your consent; or where required or authorised by law.Third PartiesWhere reasonable and practicable to do so, we will collect your Personal Information only from you. However, in some circumstances we may be provided with information by third parties. In such a case we will take reasonable steps to ensure that you are made aware of the information provided to us by the third party.Disclosure of Personal InformationYour Personal Information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following:Third parties where you consent to the use or disclosure; andWhere required or authorised by law.Security of Personal InformationYour Personal Information is stored in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.When your Personal Information is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was obtained, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your Personal Information. However, most of the Personal Information is or will be stored in client files which will be kept by us for a minimum of 7 years.Access to your Personal InformationYou may access the Personal Information we hold about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions. If you wish to access your Personal Information, please contact us in writing.Achieving the Impossible will not charge any fee for your access request, but may charge an administrative fee for providing a copy of your Personal Information.In order to protect your Personal Information we may require identification from you before releasing the requested information.Maintaining the Quality of your Personal InformationIt is an important to us that your Personal Information is up to date. We  will  take reasonable steps to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you find that the information we have is not up to date or is inaccurate, please advise us as soon as practicable so we can update our records and ensure we can continue to provide quality services to you.Policy UpdatesThis Policy may change from time to time and is available on our website.Privacy Policy Complaints and EnquiriesIf you have any queries or complaints about our Privacy Policy please contact us at: Achieving the Impossibletimothy@timothyhyde.com61 2 47588961//g.ezoic.net/privacy/expertmc.com     About Us"Hi, I'm Timothy Hyde. I'm the guy behind ExpertMC.com. I've been a professional MC for over 25 years, working all over the world. We set this site up 15 years ago to help people become better MCs and grow their MC business. Read about ExpertMC via the link below" about Featured Books The ExpertMC Toolkit & Resource Manual – A 120 page collection of Jokes, Lines, Quotes, Activities, Stories and Filler material that you can slot into any MC assignment. These are the glue that holds your MC work together. Fun introductions for guest speakers, linking material and touching Thank You’s. PLUS Pages of Advice, Tips & Techniques to help you become a great MC!  This book has helped thousands of MC’s around the world. Full Details Click Here Get Publicity Now – our brand new 6 Part Course on getting Free Publicity! Grow your business, profile and fees with these proven methods. Comes with a Bonus Action Steps Workbook to really accelerate your progress. Full Details Click Here  BWC by Timothy Hyde BWC is a short piece of fun that I perform at most of my MC Assignments around the world. It involves everyone in the audience and gets a big laugh. You can use it as an Ice Breaker, to get Attention, to wake people up or as a quick filler.   Full Details Here  This site is owned and operated by Timothy Hyde & Achieving the Impossible. We are a participant in several affiliate advertising programs. These include – Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, ClickBank and Google Adsense. As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases. We are compensated for referring traffic and business to these and other companies.
